네가 너를 단속했더라면 이런 일은 일어나지 않았을 거야
If you'd simply restrained yourself, none of this would be happening.
그냥 연락하지 말라고 말해 - 당연히 했지
Just tell her to leave you alone. - I did, I told her,
말도 하고, 문자도 보내고 트위터에도 강조해서 써놨어
I texted her, I sent out a very emphatic twitter.
페이스북에는 어떻게 써놨냐면
I even changed my Facebook status to
"쉘든 쿠퍼는 페니가 연락하지 않기를 바랍니다"라고 해놨어
더는 어떻게 해야 할지 모르겠어
I don't know what else to do.
그렇다고 나보고 어떻게 하란 거야? - 나도 몰라
Well, what am I supposed to do? - I don't know,
그렇지만 어떻게든 하지 않으면, 경고하건대
but if you don't figure something out, I warn you,
같이 살기 정말 힘들어질 거야
I shall become very difficult to live with.
그럼 지금까지는 즐겁고 행복한 쉘든이었단 말이야?
You mean up until now we've been experiencing